♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 23=
(Hechang Photography)
I'm here for Paramount's
new dancer photos.
Excuse me. I'd like to ask.
Wasn't the Paramount already closed down
and turned into a girls' school?
What do you mean?
The business is booming.
A girls' school?
What do women need to study for?
Their rightful job
is to dance and please men.
(Medicine Investigation Report)
A few days ago, I informed
the Fengcheng Chamber of Commerce
to close the Paramount
and establish a girls' school.
How does it go?
Everything is proceeding
according to your instructions.
After it's done, we will
definitely inform you, Miss Jiang.
Manager Lu of the Fengcheng Bank,
first of all, you should address me
as President Jiang.
Secondly, you should report regularly
on the tasks I've assigned,
instead of pretending to listen
while brushing me off
and informing me afterward.
Are you here to assert
your authority over us today?
We are all influential people
in the Chamber.
Jiang Chun'er, you have to listen
to whatever we say.
Do you actually think you're the head
of Fengcheng Chamber of Commerce?
What qualifications does a mere woman
have to stand above us?
My Jiang family holds the top position
in Fengcheng Chamber of Commerce
because we have the ability to.
Half of all the shops
and industries in Fengcheng
bear the Jiang name.
Who gave you the nerve
to spout nonsense in front of me?
Bah! How dare you wretch scold us?
Listen to me, Jiang Xiaoren is dead.
The shops in our hands
should now bear our names.
That's what your Jiang family owe us.
All the dirty deeds you've done
over the years are recorded here.
If these get out,
even ten lives
wouldn't be enough to save you.
(Medicine Investigation Report)
From today on, you will carry out
every task I assign diligently.
Shut down Paramount
and found a girls' school.
Also, all our merchant ships
must dock and anchor.
No foreign ships are allowed to dock.
Yes.
Let's go.
Miss Jiang,
you were so amazing just now.
I've been watching long enough.
Hong'er, do everything as I instructed.
If Xu Fan still needs money,
he won't offend my family so easily.
Wait for me to come back.
Alright.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
what our life would be like
if we weren't born in this chaotic era
and could grow up safely.
I don't think about those things.
I only focus on the present.
So what if it's a chaotic era?
As long as I can stay
in this broken temple,
this moment is the most carefree time.
(If I die,)
(you must live well for me.)
Xu Fan might move the deal up.
If Xu Fan makes the deal in advance,
then the Chamber's ships
can only hold them off for a while.
So we have to get the Jade Buddha Head
before they make the deal.
There's no time for a thorough plan.
We'll take action tonight.
If we can't get away then,
we can hide the Jade Buddha Head
in the secret passage of Master's room.
And Chun'er, you'll be our backup.
Get there before dawn.
If the Jade Buddha Head is there,
no matter what happens to us,
take the Jade Buddha Head
and leave first.
Our national treasures
must be kept in China.
You must have been mischievous
and punished outside
by your master so often
that you found this secret passage.
At least it's come in handy now.
It's explosives.
There are explosives everywhere.
These explosives don't definitely
belong to the Rongqing Troupe.
It's Xu Fan. He...
President Du,
you've seen the Jade Buddha Head.
Time to let the arms ship dock, right?
Xu Fan indeed moved the deal up.
Xu Fan set the deal location here
and planted explosives in advance.
It seems
he plans to double-cross.
Let's go.
Governor Xu, you brought so many men.
Were you afraid I'd take it by force?
President Du, you must be joking.
In business, trust must be paramount.
It's real.
President Du,
since it's real,
you must honor your promise.
President Du,
what are you doing?
Don't tell me you don't intend
to keep your word.
Where's the thing inside it?
Hurry! Catch them!
Get them!
- After them!
- Stop!
Catch them!
Hurry!
This way!
Stop!
Hurry!
Up there!
After them!
Over here!
(So the Buddha Head hid)
(this strange stone that can
amplify senses and reveal visions.)
(This could only be the heavenly stone
spoken of in ancient records.)
(Before everything is clarified,)
(the heavenly stone and the Buddha Head
mustn't fall into the wrong hands.)
Rong Xiaonan!
So I can see visions by touching
due to this heavenly stone inside.
There was never a treasure map
inside the Buddha Head.
Now is not the time to talk about this.
Let's go.
Surround this place!
Yes!
Xu You'an, what are you doing?
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪